{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "ReportPortal",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "How many custom defect types (for one defect type group) you can add to ReportPortal?",
      "correct_answer": " 10",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "5",
        "15",
        "As I wish"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": " Widgets",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What widget shows tests with the most often reason of failure Product Bug?",
      "correct_answer": " Most failed test-cases table (TOP-20) ",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Launch statistics chart",
        "Launches table",
        "Failed cases trend chart"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": " Widgets",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "How does ReportPortal calculate passing rate for the widget Passing rate summary?",
      "correct_answer": "Ratio of all passed test cases in the filter to all test cases in the filter",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ratio of all launches with status passed in the filter to all launches in the filter",
        "ReportPortal does"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "ReportPortal",
      "type": " multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": " How old ReportPortal is?",
      "correct_answer": "5 years",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2 years",
        "3 years",
        "How many I remember myself, Report Portal was"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Data base",
      "type": " multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which data base is ReportPortal using? ",
      "correct_answer": "MongoDB",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "PostgreSQL",
        "MySQL",
        "Text files"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Data base",
      "type": " multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which data base will have been used in 5.0 version of ReportPortal?",
      "correct_answer": "PostgreSQL",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "MongoDB",
        "MySQL",
        "Text files"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "ReportPortal",
      "type": " multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is the killing feature of ReportPortal?",
      "correct_answer" : "All features are killing features",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Widgets",
        "ML Analyzer",
        "Usability",
        "Real time analytics"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "ReportPortal",
      "type": " multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which is the latest ReportPortal version? ",
      "correct_answer": "4.3",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "10.1.2",
        "5.2",
        "5.0"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Data Base",
      "type": " multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "In which version ReportPortal will have moved to ReactJS and PostgreSQL?",
      "correct_answer": " 5.0",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "10.1.2",
        "5.2",
        "4.3"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "ReportPortal",
      "type": " multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is common between Homer Simpson and Report Portal?",
      "correct_answer": "All answers are correct",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Can predict future",
        "Everybody loves",
        "Well drawn",
        "Donuts"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "ReportPortal",
      "type": " multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Where you can find test parameters in ReportPortal?",
      "correct_answer": "Step view",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Launch view",
        "Suite view",
        "There is no test parameters in ReportPortal"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Integrations",
      "type": " multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "How many integrations with test frameworks does ReportPortal have?",
      "correct_answer": "23",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "4",
        "82",
        "9"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Integrations",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Does ReportPortal have an integration with Cucumber 2?",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Integrations",
      "type": " multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Does ReportPortal have an integration with NightwatchJS?",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "ReportPortal",
      "type": " multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What ReportPortal is?",
      "correct_answer": "AI-powered Test Automation Dashboard",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Management system ",
        "Accounting system",
        "Portal with reports"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "BTS",
      "type": " multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which Bug Tracking System does ReportPortal work with?",
      "correct_answer": "Rally, Jira",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Rally, Jira, TFS",
        "Rally, Jira, TFS, Bugzilla",
        "No integrations with BTS"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Analyzer",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Are launches in Debug mode counted in the Auto-Analysis?",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "ReportPortal",
      "type": " multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What role is not in Report Portal?",
      "correct_answer": "Tester",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Member",
        "PM ",
        "Customer"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "BTS",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Could you post issues with type Epic to Jira from ReportPortal?",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "ReportPortal",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Could you add .HAR as an attachment to ReportPortal?",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Analyzer",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which log levels are taken into account by Analyzer?",
      "correct_answer": "Error and higher",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "All levels",
        "only Error and Info",
        "Trace and higher"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Analyzer",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Can you reset the accumulated experience of the Analyzer?",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]
}